manyavar.com 2014-10-24

# Privacy Policy | Manyavar

We are Manyavar.com, a service provided by Vedant fashions Pvt.Ltd. from, Kolkata, West Bengal, India. In this Privacy Policy, references to “you” mean any person submitting any data to us or our agent or the Site.

If you have any comments or suggestions, we would be pleased to receive them at Vedant Fashions Private Limited, A501-A502, SDF-1, 4th Floor, Paridhan Garment Park, 19 Canal South Road, Kolkata-700 015 or by emailing us at [cc@manyavar.com.](mailto:cc@manyavar.com)

Data protection is a matter of trust and your privacy is important to us. We shall therefore only use your name and other information which relates to you in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. We will only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so and we will only collect information if it is relevant to our dealings with you.

We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.

You can visit the Site and browse without having to provide personal details. During your visit to the Site you remain anonymous and at no time can we identify you unless you have an account on the Site and log on with your user name and password.

Data that we collect   
We may collect various information if you seek to place an order for a product to us on the Site. We collect, store and process your data for processing your purchase on the Site and any possible later claims, and to provide you with our services. We may collect your title, name, gender, email address, postal address, delivery address (if different), telephone number, mobile number, fax number, payment details, payment card details or bank account details.

We need this information in order to allow you to go ahead with placing your order for a product. We may use that data to process payment for the product and deliver the product to you. We also use that data to inform you when the product is about to be delivered.

We may pass your name and address on to a third party in order to make delivery of the product to you (for example to our courier or supplier) with or without your consent.

We may also share your data with our franchisee. We further authorise the franchisee to use this information to sell products to you, directly or indirectly.

We may also use your data in order to manage the Site, collect payment from you, enable you to subsequently use parts of the Site, detect any fraud or Site abuses, send you information relevant to the Site or our products, and in case we have any queries. Payments that you make through the Site will be processed by the CC Avenue.

You must only submit to us or our agent or the Site information which is accurate and not misleading and you must keep it up to date and inform us of changes.

Your actual order details may be stored with us and you may access this information by logging into your account on the Site. Here you can view the details of your orders that have been completed, those which are open and those which are shortly to be dispatched and administer your address details, bank details and any newsletter to which you may have subscribed. We undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties. We cannot assume any liability for misuse of passwords unless this misuse is our fault.

We shall not share any of your personal information with third parties without your explicit consent. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent and we only use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. We view protection of your privacy as a very important community principle. We understand clearly that you and Your Information is one of our most important assets. We store and process Your Information on computers located in the India that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices. We use third parties to verify and certify our privacy principles. If you object to your Information being transferred or used in this way please do not use the site.

Under no circumstances do we rent, trade or share your personal information that we have collected with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

Check Credit and Fraud Prevention  
We use standard and authorized payment services and our Credit Check and Fraud Prevention policies are aligned to these companies.

Any dispute arising out of this Privacy Policy will be referred to the Courts of Kolkata and it shall have the jurisdiction to entertain and try all actions and proceedings arising out of this Policy.

Other uses of your personal information  
We may also send you other information about us, the Site, our other websites, our products, sales promotions, our newsletters, SMS updates, anything relating to other companies in our group or our business partners. If you would prefer not to receive any of this additional information as detailed in this paragraph (or any part of it) please click the “unsubscribe” link in any email that we send to you or follow the unsubscription process as detailed in the SMS. Kindly note that unsubscribing from one medium does not automatically lead to unsubscription from the other.. Within 7 working days (days which are neither (i) a Saturday or Sunday, nor (ii) a public holiday anywhere in India) of receipt of your instruction we will cease to send you information as requested. If your instruction is unclear we will contact you for clarification.

Competitions  
For any competition we use the data to notify winners and advertise our offers. You can find more details where applicable in our participation terms for the respective competition.

Third Parties and Links  
We may pass your details to other companies in our group. We may also pass your details to our agents and subcontractors to help us with any of our uses of your data set out in our Privacy Policy with or without your consent. For example, we may use third parties to assist us with delivering products to you, to help us to collect payments from you, to analyze data and to provide us with marketing or customer service assistance. We may exchange information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We may transfer our databases containing your personal information if we sell our business or part of it. Other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, we shall NOT sell or disclose your personal data to third parties without obtaining your prior consent unless this is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or unless we are required to do so by law.

Links to other web sites:  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. Please note that we do not have any control over those websites. We are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such websites and such websites are not governed by this privacy policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy applicable to the website in question. We shall not be liable for any dispute arising between you and the Third Party for whatsoever reason, in connection with the Third Party’s Privacy policy.

Cookies  
The acceptance of cookies is not a requirement for visiting the Site. However we would like to point out that the some functionality on the Site and ordering is only possible with the activation of cookies. Cookies are tiny text files which identify your computer to our server as a unique user when you visit certain pages on the Site and they are stored by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to recognize your Internet Protocol address, saving you time while you are on, or want to enter, the Site. We only use cookies for your convenience in using the Site (for example to remember who you are when you want to amend your shopping cart without having to re-enter your email address) and not for obtaining or using any other information about you (for example targeted advertising). Your browser can be set to not accept cookies, but this would restrict your use of the Site. Please accept our assurance that our use of cookies does not contain any personal or private details and are free from viruses. If you want to find out more information about cookies, go tohttp://www.allaboutcookies.org or to find out about removing them from your browser, go to http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html.

The Site uses technology from Google Analytics through which data is collected and stored for marketing and optimization purposes and data use profiles are prepared under a pseudonym. Cookies may be used for this. The cookies enable recognition of the Internet browser. The data collected with these technologies is not used, without separate authorization by the person concerned, to personally identify the visitors to this website and is not collated with personal data on the pseudonym holder. The permission for data recording and storage may at any time be cancelled with on-going effect.

Security  
We have in place appropriate technical and security measures to prevent unauthorised or unlawful access to or accidental loss of or destruction or damage to your information. When we collect data through the Site, we collect your personal details on a secure server. We use firewalls on our servers. When we collect payment card details electronically, we use encryption by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) coding. Whilst we are unable to guarantee 100% security, this makes it hard for a hacker to decrypt your details. You are strongly recommended not to send full credit or debit card details in unencrypted electronic communications. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. You are responsible for protecting against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer.

Online Privacy Policy  
This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Consent  
By submitting data to us or our agent or using the Site, you consent to our use of your data in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

Copyright  
We have copyright over this Privacy Policy. Use by third parties, even by way of extract, for commercial purposes is not allowed. Infringements may be subject to legal action. This Privacy Policy can amend/ change at any time to include / exclude clauses. Your continued use of our website following any such amendments / changes will be deemed to be confirmation that you accept those amendments and manyavar.com does not bear responsibility for updating Users on the same.

Legal Disclaimer:  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and / or to comply with judicial proceeding, Court order or legal process served on our website.

Contacting us:  
If there are any question regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:-  
**Address:** Vedant Fashions Private Limited, A501-A502, SDF-1, 4th Floor, Paridhan Garment Park, 19 Canal South Road, Kolkata-700 015.   
**Email Address:** [info@manyavar.com](mailto:info@manyavar.com)   
**Contact:** +91 33 2323 5353 , 09038045353
